Today, the second item is in the case of our pastor of First Assembly of God,
church-raining for Zell.
Pastor, thanks for being here.
Honor to be here.
It's about to get a final witness.
Thank you for your grace upon our lives.
We wish you blessed this evening as we face this national day.
I pray that you would just grace our nation,
with your presence, Lord God, our national leaders,
or our state leaders, and especially here tonight,
our city leaders who pay you, just give them your wisdom.
Our Lord, you pray that you would bless our businesses,
Lord, I'm pleased to broaden our fight department,
the city servants here.
Let's our church-raise, Lord Jesus,
and may your love just continue to touch this city.
We thank you, Lord, for all that you do in our midst,
and when you ask you, crown this evening with your presence,
in Jesus' name.
Amen.
I want to thank you.
That would you please join me.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America,
and to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation, another God,
the United States of America, to the United States of Iran.
Okay.
Item four is the Republic input,
and unscheduled personal appearances,
and anyone in the audience, it wishes to address the authority
on any of the agenda items.
Being none, item five is considered to be in the staff
as recommending item six through ten,
if there are no questions on these items,
so we have a motion.
My answer is not a objection on that motion.
Thank you.
Second.
Roll call.
Question.
Hi.
For a stir.
All right.
Item 11 is new business, and any of you business dean?
Not of anybody out there.
Staff reports that are in your packet,
and the staff is available for any questions.
They're being non-created announcements,
any announcements.
Item 14 is motion two adjourn.
Do we have a motion adjourn?
Motion adjourn.
And I'll second that roll call.
I'm sorry you picked the question.
Question.
I can show.
Hi.
Johnson.
Okay.
Do we need a...